const quizQuestions = {
    questions: [
        {
          question:
          "Which is the Capital Of PAKISTAN?",
          choices: [
            "Lahore",
            "Karachi",
            "Islamabad",
            "Peshawar",
          ],
          type: "MCQs",
          correctAnswer: "Islamabad",
        },
        {
            question:
            "Where is situated Minar-E-Pakistan?",
            choices: [
              "Lahore",
              "Gujranwala",
              "Multan",
              "Sialkot",
            ],
            type: "MCQs",
            correctAnswer: "Lahore",
          },
          {
            question:
            "Which is the largest province Of PAKISTAN in terms of population?",
            choices: [
              "Sindh",
              "Khyber-Pakhtunkhwa",
              "Balochistan",
              "Punjab",
            ],
            type: "MCQs",
            correctAnswer: "Punjab",
          },
          {
            question:
            "Which is the largest city Of PAKISTAN?",
            choices: [
              "Lahore",
              "Karachi",
              "Gujranwala",
              "Multan",
            ],
            type: "MCQs",
            correctAnswer: "Karachi",
          },
          {
            question:
            "Which is the National Game Of PAKISTAN?",
            choices: [
              "Hockey",
              "Cricket",
              "Badminton",
              "VolleyBall",
            ],
            type: "MCQs",
            correctAnswer: "Hockey",
          },
          {
            question:
            "Which city of PAKISTAN is Famous For Rice?",
            choices: [
              "Jehlam",
              "Wazirabad",
              "Hafizabad",
              "Gujrat",
            ],
            type: "MCQs",
            correctAnswer: "Hafizabad",
          },
          {
            question:
            "Which city of PAKISTAN is Famous For Manufacturing Sports Goods?",
            choices: [
              "Lahore",
              "Gujranwala",
              "Hafizabad",
              "Sialkot",
            ],
            type: "MCQs",
            correctAnswer: "Sialkot",
          },
          {
            question:
            "Which city of PAKISTAN is Called the City of Wrestlers?",
            choices: [
              "LalaMusa",
              "Gujranwala",
              "Multan",
              "Gujrat",
            ],
            type: "MCQs",
            correctAnswer: "Gujranwala",
          },
          {
            question:
            "Which is The National Animal of PAKISTAN?",
            choices: [
              "Fox",
              "Elephant",
              "Markhor",
              "Lion",
            ],
            type: "MCQs",
            correctAnswer: "Markhor",
          },
          {
            question:
            "Which is the Largest Country in the World?",
            choices: [
              "America",
              "Russia",
              "Canada",
              "Italy",
            ],
            type: "MCQs",
            correctAnswer: "Russia",
          }
    ]
}
export default quizQuestions;